https://www.t-plan.com/privacy-policy/

Who we are
Our website address is: www.t-plan.com.
T-Plan’s websites can be used without entering any personal information. Certian sections on our site, however, can collect personal information from you (e.g. name, address, email address, telephone number, etc.) in accordance with UK data protection (GDPR), and these are detailed in the sections below.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
T-Plan uses a contact form plugin. We collect information from you when you visit our site, subscribe to our blog or forums, our newsletter or complete a form, or when you email us. When completing a form you may be asked to enter your name and email address.
The information we collect through our forms may be used in the following ways:
To personalise your experience;
To improve our website;
To administer your interest in our products or services;
To send relevant emails.
Cookies
Cookies are small text files that your internet browser downloads and store on your computer. These cookies are used to improve our website services. In most cases, these are so-called “session cookies” and get deleted once you leave our website. Some cookies, however, also pass along information used to recognize you automatically. Recognition occurs through an IP address saved to the cookies. The information obtained is used to improve our services. You can prevent cookies from being installed by adjusting the settings on your browser software. You should be aware, however, that by doing so, you may not be able to make full use of all the functions of our website.
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Livezilla
T-Plan’s websites uses third party software to provide live chat bots. This software uses cookies in order to recognize repeat use of our website by the same user/internet connection subscriber. The cookies for Livezilla are listed below:
Name
Provider
Purpose
Lifetime
Type
Category
lz_geo_city
LiveZilla GmbH
Geolocation (City), used to determine the geographical location of website visitors.
1 Year
HTTP Cookie
Statistic
lz_geo_ctryiso
LiveZilla GmbH
Geolocation (Country), used to determine the geographical location of website visitors.
1 Year
HTTP Cookie
Statistic
lz_geo_data
LiveZilla GmbH
Geolocation (Timestamp), used to determine the geographical location of website visitors.
1 Year
HTTP Cookie
Statistic
lz_geo_isp
LiveZilla GmbH
Geolocation (ISP), used to determine the geographical location of website visitors.
1 Year
HTTP Cookie
Statistic
lz_geo_lat
LiveZilla GmbH
Geolocation (Latitude), used to determine the geographical location of website visitors.
1 Year
HTTP Cookie
Statistic
lz_geo_long
LiveZilla GmbH
Geolocation (Longitude), used to determine the geographical location of website visitors.
1 Year
HTTP Cookie
Statistic
lz_geo_region
LiveZilla GmbH
Geolocation (Region), used to determine the geographical location of website visitors.
1 Year
HTTP Cookie
Statistic
lz_geo_tz
LiveZilla GmbH
Geolocation (Timezone), used to determine the geographical location of website visitors.
1 Year
HTTP Cookie
Statistic
lz_last_visit
LiveZilla GmbH
Last Visit (Timestamp), used to determine when the website visitor browsed the website the last time.
1 Year
HTTP Cookie
Statistic
lz_userid
LiveZilla GmbH
Sets up a unique ID which is used to generate statistical data about the website visitor’s usage of the website.
1 Year
HTTP Cookie
Statistic
lz_visits
LiveZilla GmbH
Number of visits, is used to identify how often the website visitor already visited the website.
1 Year
HTTP Cookie
Statistic
cookie_accepted
LiveZilla GmbH
Used to determine if website visitor has confirmed data privacy / cookie notification.
1 Year
HTTP Cookie
Required
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
T-Plan collects data and analyses this activity via Google Analytics, visitor forensics solutions (WhoIsVisiting , Lead Forensics) and Yoast SEO. T-Plan does not personally or directly identify you when you visit our website. This information may include the content you view, the date and time that you view this content, the products you browse, or your location information associated with your IP Address. We use this information we collect for marketing purposes in establishing statistics on user traffic on our website.
With each visit to our website we may automatically collect the following information:
Technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the internet, time zone setting, browser types and versions, operating system and platform.
Information about your website visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our site (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks etc.).
Who we share your data with
T-Plan only uses information as defined in this policy, this means we will never sell, trade or otherwise share your identifiable or anonymised information. This does not include trusted third parties that support us in our business operations, as long as these partners comply with our privacy guidelines.
Identifiable information includes information which can be used to identify you. Examples of identifiable information are your name, email address, your address and phone number.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
We intend to retain data from contacts until they revoke that privilege. Customer data will be stored for a maximum of 5 years in order to comply with requirements around reporting and accounting, but also in order to provide customers with data on previous engagements etc.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your contact information
The information collected may be processed in the following ways:
The information you provide may include your name, work address, email address and phone number, financial and credit card information, personal and work details.
We may use the information provided to fulfil obligations resulting from contracts entered into between you and T-Plan.
We may use the information provided to make you aware of other products or services what you have already purchased or enquired about.
We may receive information about you from other sources. This may include for example if you use any of our other company websites, or from the other services we provide. We are also working closely with third parties; including, for example, business partners, and we may receive information about you from them.
If you have specific privacy concerns please contact us at support@t-plan.com.
You can unsubscribe from our emails at any time. We include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each marketing email. Additionally, you can email sales@t-plan.com to unsubscribe. You have the right to see what data we have collected, and you have the right to request removal of this data, simply email sales@t-plan.com with your request.
Source: WPML
WPML uses cookies to identify the visitor’s current language, the last visited language and the language of users who have logged in.
While you use the plugin, WPML will share data regarding the site through Installer. No data from the user itself will be shared.
Source: YouTube
Our website uses plugins from YouTube, which is operated by Google. The operator of the pages is YouTube LLC, 901 Cherry Ave., San Bruno, CA 94066, USA.
If you visit one of our pages featuring a YouTube plugin, a connection to the YouTube servers is established. Here the YouTube server is informed about which of our pages you have visited.
If you’re logged in to your YouTube account, YouTube allows you to associate your browsing behavior directly with your personal profile. You can prevent this by logging out of your YouTube account.
YouTube is used to help make our website appealing. This constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO.
Further information about handling user data, can be found in the data protection declaration of YouTube under https://www.google.de/intl/de/policies/privacy.
Google Web Fonts
For uniform representation of fonts, this page uses web fonts provided by Google. When you open a page, your browser loads the required web fonts into your browser cache to display texts and fonts correctly.
For this purpose your browser has to establish a direct connection to Google servers. Google thus becomes aware that our web page was accessed via your IP address. The use of Google Web fonts is done in the interest of a uniform and attractive presentation of our plugin. This constitutes a justified interest pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f) DSGVO.
If your browser does not support web fonts, a standard font is used by your computer.
Further information about handling user data, can be found at https://developers.google.com/fonts/faq and in Google’s privacy policy at https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/.
SEO
Website Marketing is provided by Newtide Digital.
Disclaimer
The content provided on this site is on an ‘as is’ and ‘as available’ basis, and T-Plan assumes no responsibility for its accuracy or reliability. All content on this site is for general information purposes only, and although we try to keep this content up to date and correct, we make no warranties, expressed or implied about the accuracy, reliability, suitability, or availability with respect of the website, its content, or related graphics it contains for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.
In no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, or any loss or damage whatsoever arising from loss of data or profits arising out of, or in connection with, the use of this website.
Unit 8, Lady Bee Enterprise Centre,
Albion Street, Southwick,
Brighton.
East Sussex.
BN42 4BW.
United Kingdom.Dedicated UK Sales, Support & Training Number:
0203 745 2020
From outside the UK please call: +44 (0)203 745 2020sales@t-plan.com
T-Plan Automation for RPA & QA T-Plan Automation for RPA & QA updated their business hours.www.facebook.com View on Facebook·ShareShare on FacebookShare on TwitterShare on Linked InShare by EmailT-Plan Automation for RPA & QA T-Plan Automation for RPA & QA updated their website address.www.facebook.com View on Facebook·ShareShare on FacebookShare on TwitterShare on Linked InShare by Email
Blog
T-Plan Opens Office in Brighton
Test Management Application for a Mac
CAD Test Automation using Paraview
Image Based versus Object Oriented Testing
The Seven Deadly Sins
© 2018 All rights reserved. T-Plan Limited
Privacy Policy
